Hi, this is Haru.
I'm here in Harajuku!
I moved to Tokyo this spring after graduating from high school.
I graduated from high school and wanted to hang out around here.
I need some strong help, you know... it's not easy to do it alone.
So I'd like to go that way for a while.
I'm working on something right now.
Wow, now...
I'm here in Harajuku.
I'm here, but didn't you come to Takeshita-dori?
Yes, I did.
That's the entrance to Meiji Shrine.
Have you been to Takeshita-dori?
I have, but only as a family.
I've come to the conclusion that Takeshita-dori is that way.
This way.
Huh.
Phew.
Well, let's go.
Shall we go then?
I know it's out of the blue, but...
Yes, let's go, then.
Oh, my gosh.
I haven't been in junior high since I was in high school.
Takeshita... Harajuku? Harajuku? Takeshita Street.
I asked why you wanted to come.
As a reason...
I was scouted here. Takeshita-dori.
Takeshita-dori?
Yes.
I want to go there.
I want to go to Takeshita-dori.
Yeah?
No, I'm good.
Okay.
So... shopping in Harajuku?
Oh, Ah,
I'm going to go get some clothes and stuff.
Okay.
Take Takeshita-dori in Harajuku.
Straight down Harajuku Takeshita Street.
Okay, okay, okay.
It's called Urahara.
Urahara?
Well, you know... fashionable...
Oh, uh...
You know, where there's traps and stuff.
I didn't want that.
Fashionable.
Oh, I think it's right here.
Yes, it is.
We're here.
Traitor
gentler
acker
As soon as possible.
I'd like to go there.
There's a lot of people here.
What's the matter?
It's stylish, isn't it?
It's a little different from how I remember it.
It's different from how I remember it.
There's a lot of crepes and stuff.
I have an image of something sweet.
I went there because I was hungry.
I need something to eat.
There's another song playing.
This one.
Oh, my God.
What a coincidence.
It's playing, though.
Thank you.
You have this encounter in Harajuku.
Crepe. crepe
crepe
There's a line for these.
They're so good!
There used to be a dance school I went to.
Here?
Let's eat just in case.
Let's get in line.
Look at this.
The structure of this menu.
Is it too much to ask?
I was scouted out around here.
What? Again? Around here?
I was talking to a guy who approached me.
Well, the first time. The first time anyway.
What do you mean, the first time?
Well, the first time anyway.
Well, well, well. First scout.
And I'm like, "What am I gonna say?
She was talking to your mother, not me.
I didn't know what was going on.
At the time, I didn't know what he was talking about.
Now I wish I had listened to her.
Were you in show business then, by the way?
What? No, really.
I didn't.
You really weren't interested?
Like really into soccer?
Yeah, I'm already with the soccer boys.
Oh, did you dance?
Uh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'm sorry, can I make a decision?
Uh, sorry, sorry.
That's great.
I'm torn.
I don't know. It's like... I mean, it's not like a sweet, you know?
Pizza.
Let's just have one for the both of us. Let's make it a two-for-one.
One for the both of us?
Sweets out of the blue.
Is Harajuku a dreamland?
It's so exciting.
It's a dreamland.
I'm so excited!
This looks so good!
Here you go.
You brought it!
Bon appétit!
I feel like a man. Yum! Bananas are so good! Bananas are so good!
Even the dough is good. I wasn't really good at prep before.
This is so good!
It's on your pretty mouth.
Bananas.
Yum.
And clothes, too.
I know, right?
Amazing.
Like potatoes.
Palm reading?
Touch it with your left hand.
Touch it for 10 seconds.
It'll take the bad jackets out of your body.
It's a really good one.
It's going to be a success in the arena.
Oh!
Rainbow, the longest in Japan... while you know... this is a long longe ronge ronge guest.
I'll totally eat it!
Shall we get in line?
Can I take this?
Excuse me.
Is it okay if I know the teacher in the restaurant?
Longa, you know...
It's more like...
Longer
Longer than, the longest. Longer than the longest, the longest
So, that's why it's a long-long-gallon guest.
That's what it means.
I remember.
You remember?
English. I was the only one who took it all three years in high school.
Oh, you did?
Yes, I never used it for entertainment.
Well, maybe I'll put in this version of Good.
Good?
Gooder.
Oh, wait.
No, look, if we don't do it the way we think it should be done...
Gooder.
Gooder. Goodesso.
What would you like to buy, by the way?
Uh, this... this is the longest one.
No, it's too loud.
Gross.
That's amazing.
He's a master of his craft.
No one can imitate that!
It's a proper potato!
Wow, they're huge!
Wow!
Look at this!
I just wanted to thank you ladies for all the help you gave me with the mecos.
I asked them for a commercial and a questionnaire.
We have a long, long one!
I'm going to pose a lot for that.
Can I have a Meko? While it's still warm.
I'm going to have a big bowl of Ka!
It's so good!
Is it good?
Yes, it's good.
It's like Pepco.
Oh, yes, yes, yes.
It's so good! I'm so good at this!
I don't know about you, but I don't want to be bothered.
Ka-ha-ha-ha!
It was really delicious.
I ate it all without thinking about the calories
No, no, no, no, you know there's a Harajuku map? Isn't it great?
This is where I was scouted the second time I drove here
So it's the same guy? No, it's not the same person. That day? The same day?
The same day. Wow, that's great.
He took me to a corner.
Yes, he took me around the corner.
Next is my main goal... to get to know the robots a little better.
There, there, there, there, there, there, there.
There it is! Animatronic!
What's that? A place where you can meet Rajin's robots.
Can we take pictures inside?
Oh! Shooting! Yes, yes, it's okay. Here comes A Venture!
Here it comes! Here it comes!
Enjoy the show!
Cute!
Look at this.
Honeymooners have their day.
I dodged a guinea pig.
So cute.
Here's a kiss.
That's the best shot I've ever seen.
It's a service shot.
It's so relaxing.
Oh, my God, that's so relaxing.
I'm going to feed him.
Let's feed him.
I'm sorry.
Don't hurt me, don't hurt me
Don't hurt me, don't hurt me.
So cute
Look at all that food!
Here it comes! Here it comes!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I dropped it Sorry, sorry, I dropped it.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
You made a bowl with your hands
That's scary.
Oh no!
The girls at the store don't stand up needles at all
Actually, it doesn't hurt so much with bare hands.
I rolled it up!
It's such a cute bandage!
I feel like I'm playing with a little girl.
It's that soothing.
It's so soothing.
This place is amazing!
Please come here!
Please come.
Thank you very much.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's like...
I didn't know.
It's good, right?
Here.
I didn't know about Harajuku.
I didn't know. I didn't know a millimeter of it.
I didn't know.
I didn't know this existed.
Oh, my God.
I've been around a lot.
Touching the animals.
Eat fries.
And eat.
We ate at the café.
Eat.
This was a random plan, right?
It's just random.
And filming.
I asked him to do it this way.
I asked him to help us out on a moment's notice. Suddenly you're cooperating with me.
You're making me think twice about Harajuku.
I don't know...
It's more like...
Family
I'd say it's more of an indie style.
I see.
I'll come back next time.
Not at all.
He's coming.
And I've only been to...
I've only been to about three stores.
That's right.
It's taking a while.
Yeah.
It's good to have a plan.
It would be nice.
That's true.
Don't plan anything.
It's nice.
It's good to just go with a plan.
I think it's a good idea.
I've been thinking about it a little more.
We have everything.
Who the hell do you think you are?
I'm Takeshita-dori.
I looked it over.
You're right.
There's everything.
Me...
Takeshita-dori.
I was scouted there.
It's where I remember.
I see.
There it is.
Please make a pilgrimage to the holy place
And...
Chinchilla. chinchilla
guinea pig
Hamsters
Let's buy a house
See you soon.